[Music]
Sholay Sholay se ho
yaar maine itni moti ring pehna rahi hai
hello everyone namaste and welcome back to my
second channel yes ji guys this is my second
channel and if you haven't subscribed then
why not guys look at the views of Hawaii
so blue blue sky and blue blue
water anyway guys this is my beach
outfit today but the best thing is the
view from here.  Look at this.
[MUSIC] It's
sunny so I'm wearing this cap
that I got as a birthday gift.  There are a
lot of things to do today
but first let's have breakfast
because I haven't had coffee yet and my
brain is not working.
Here is a great cafe in front of the beach.
We have breakfast here.
You get me hanging in.
Ganna Get This One French Toast and Coffee P O
O N A
[Music]
I told him clearly my name is Poonam.
Guys, it's written Poha here.  Yes so
milk coffee.
Look who is in front of me?  Bro bro bro
no
didi please give me a little.
Friend, why are you not letting me eat my food comfortably
?  Brother, there was food there too.
Why have you come here?  My
people around me are eating a lot of food.  And
why has this pigeon come to my table only?
Cheers,
here's another one and I have one in front of me,
so this one is French toast
[music] and it has different fruits on top.
Strawberries, blueberries, flowers
you can eat, and here's a banana.
He said that you can eat this flower.
But I don't know.
Actually there is no test.  Meaning it
feels like you are not eating anything
but there is no bad taste.  Had fun.
Before I leave, I have to buy gifts for some friends and family.
So here is
Sunier's shop.  You get awesome things here.
So let's do some shopping.  Guys,
this is a postcard from Hawaii.  Looks simple,
right?  But look at these ones.  Oh my God.
Why do I have to see all this?  Well,
I am blind.
I'm gonna get this one.  This one is also this
Hala Lai.  These people make and wear the famous flower and
its garland.
I ate this flower for breakfast today,
but this one is a hairpin.
So we will take this one also.  Will it
look cute?  Can I have a basket?
I have asked aunty for chabadi.  Thank you very much.
This is a necklace and the shark tooth is
here.  Guys, this
glass is so cute.
She is wearing the bikini, man.  The
glasses here are also so obscene.  Is a
camera.
Can you turn
the other side the
other side.
Oh yes.  It moves automatically like you can
turn like this.  And or I Wish It Could Call It
But It's Only a Camera.  Like you can just
talk and record.  [laughter]
You're kid, where are you from?
South Korea.
I live in South India
[laughs]
These flowers, hair clips, these
are very popular in India, I
want this bracelet to match my outfit, guys,
I have also got this one
which moves like this.  This is the typical
dance here.  [MUSIC] Dress like this and
dance like this.  Dono Trump
I think this bracelet looks better than
this one.  But it
is very expensive.  This
also gets me this for the collection for my fridge.  Cute
isn't it?  Whenever I go somewhere,
I always bring the magnets for the fridge
and put them on my fridge.
I
also need earrings for my outfit.  These are the Denkel ones and
these ones are just like that, I ca
n't understand which one looks good
[laughs]
that one is very small so I buy these small ones [music] I
only buy these things because there are
many other stores nearby so I will
check them out too
so much
she so sweet.  [Music] He asked if I had a
husband or not, if I was married or not?
Dude, I am wearing such a thick ring.
All these people think that I am married
but I am not.  Dude, can't a girl buy a diamond with her own money
?  Now I am
tired of telling people that I am
alone, guys.  Guys here at Open
Market.  So there are a lot of
cool things available here too.  So let's
take some small gift from here also.  Guys this
doll is making $4 here.  That
first Korean aunty gave me $4 extra,
meaning the price was printed there.
Is there a real one?
Or We Are Three.
Oh!  So I got this one fresh guys it's cute is
n't it I needed something white for my white outfit
where are you from
Korea yes [laughs]
I live in Korea
this one is also from Anti Korea
okay guys
I told them that I am from Korea
so they
gave me a bracelet for free.  Guys, here you can get that
Hawaiian t-shirt for dogs.   It's
$25.  Mangomo is more expensive.  We don't have
that much money.  Sorry Mango.  We're
not so rich that I can afford to dress you in a $25
t-shirt that I can get online for $5.
In the Doors
[Music]
Guys, this one's a Tesla robot.
Meetic [music]
[sound of singing]
Skin
[music]
Guys the water is so clear here.  Oh my
God.
You can sit there in the sun if you want,
or you can sleep under the shade of this big tree
like [music] where some people are sleeping here.
O S
[Music]
De
I G
[Music]
Room Let's go
to this cafe called
Goofy.
This is a very healthy ball avocado cell
spinner
[music]
[song voice]
Man, America is very expensive.  You have to
give a tip here.  Guys I am back to
my hotel and now I am getting ready to go back to the airport Korea.
Guys,
I'm really tanned after coming here
but I feel good.  So let me tell you one
good thing about the American people.  So
basically, American people don't like you if you are too fair.
They
say that your
colour is like that of a dead body and on the contrary, when they tan, they get a
little brown golden skin and
they like that more.
That is why they keep themselves outside in the sun all day long,
but
in Korea and I think in India too, the fair complexion, the
clear complexion, is
considered more beautiful.  I always
use this small sponge.  Finger Sponge Technically this one is
its sponge but much bigger.  Let me
tell you another interesting thing, there are
many Korean people here who have come to visit.
And the Korean people here,
they wear totally long sleeves
and long pants when they go to the sea so that
they do not get black.
That's the sad reality.  Will
not apply lipstick or mascara.  I will only apply eyeliner.
[MUSIC] I always forget something
whenever I leave the hotel.  And it is
not that some small thing happened.  That means
I forget all the things like jewellery, gold, silver, diamonds etc.  So this time I
want to check a little better.
On my last white trip, I lost my fear
bracelet.  Which
I bought for a literal trip.  And
guys I'm ready now and let's check
out.
I can do it.  Good Good Dole Sholay Come Guys
I have reached the airport.  I have got my luggage packed
and now let's go to the lawn.
Come back after eating yummy food.  By the guys, do
tell me in the comments how my today's outfit looks.
[Music]
Ma
Guys, this bathroom is really cool.
Here you will get the pads for free.
So here it is.  Friend,
why is it not coming out?  So here it is.  Right now
I'm going to eat lots of yummy food and
sleep [music] and you'll see me
directly in Korea.  See You
In Korea Guys.  Bye.
I got this bag in the first class
and inside it is a toy.
Tissue paper ice and cute slippers have also been
found.
[soundbite of song]
[music]
Nika
De
[music] Sam [soundbite of song]
[music]
I'm home but look how much
packaging has come in front of my house.  I
put all this stuff inside.  And that's all Gaius
came for today.  Hope you
liked today's weird vlog too.  I am
so tired.  I can't tell you.
My eyes are burning.  I am so
tired but it doesn't matter.  I
hope you liked today's vlog, so please
tell us your favorite part in the comments.
And like I'm next video
the
[music]
or some business yeah.  I am doing some business there.
I have some coins let me
say ok guys I am scared that a pigeon might
suddenly eat my food guys the boys are
crazy about me even the pigeons
turned out to be crazy about me
Shanti.